wecustomers.com 2015-12-21

# Privacy Policy - We Customers

**WeCustomers.com Principles**

Here at WeCustomers.com, we believe strongly in openness and trust. The more we trust each other by being open and honest, the more we all can benefit from our collective experiences. We hope this is reflected in our privacy policy below.

**The Information We Collect**

When you visit WeCustomers.com, you provide us with two types of information: personal information you knowingly choose to disclose that is collected by us, and website use information collected by us as you interact with the WeCustomers.com website. When you register with WeCustomers.com, you provide us with certain personal information, such as your name and email address. When you enter WeCustomers.com, we may collect your browser type and IP address. This information is gathered for all WeCustomers.com visitors but will be kept private and not used to track individual activity and only be used to deter spammers or otherwise improve the WeCustomers.com experience. In addition, we may store information from your browser using "cookies." A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information about the user. We may use session ID cookies to confirm that users are logged in. These cookies terminate once the user closes the browser. We may use a persistent cookie that stores your login ID and password, to make it easier for you to login when you come back to WeCustomers.com. You can remove or block this cookie using the settings in your browser, if you want to disable this convenience feature.

When you use WeCustomers.com, you may set up your personal profile, form relationships, send messages, perform searches and queries, submit questions/answers, and transmit information through various channels. We collect this information so we can provide you with high-quality service and offer personalized features. In most cases, we retain it so that, for instance, you can return to view prior messages you have sent or easily see your friends list.

You post all Posted Content (as defined in the WeCustomers.com Terms of Use) the WeCustomers.com website at your own risk. Although we allow you to set privacy options that limit access to your pages, please be aware that no security measures for any website are impenetrable or 100% secure. We cannot control the actions of other users with whom you may choose to share your pages and information. Therefore, we cannot and do not guarantee that Posted Content on the WeCustomers.com website will not be viewed by unauthorized persons. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the WeCustomers.com website. You understand and acknowledge that, even after removal, copies of Posted Content may remain viewable in cached and archived pages or if other users have copied or stored your Posted Content.

Any improper collection or misuse of information provided on WeCustomers.com is a violation of the WeCustomers.com Terms of Service and should be reported to admin@wecustomers.com

If you choose to use our invitation service to tell a friend about our website, we will ask you for your friend's email address. We will automatically send your friend an email inviting him or her to visit the site. WeCustomers.com stores this information to send this email, to register a friend connection if your invitation is accepted, and to track the success of our referral program. Your friend may contact us at infowecustomers.com to request that we remove this information from our database.

WeCustomers.com may also collect information about you from other sources, such as newspapers, blogs, instant messaging services, and other users of the WeCustomers.com service through the operation of the service (e.g., photo tags) in order to provide you with more useful information and a more personalized experience.

By using WeCustomers.com, you consent to have your personal data transferred to and processed in the United States.

**Children Under Age 13**

WeCustomers.com does not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 13 or knowingly allow such persons to register. If you are under 13, please do not attempt to register for WeCustomers.com or send any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number or email address. No one under age 13 may provide any personal information to or on WeCustomers.com. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information as quickly as possible.

**Children Between Ages of 13 and 18**

We recommend that minors over the age of 13 ask their parents for permission before sending any information about themselves to anyone over the Internet.

**Use of Information Obtained by WeCustomers.com**

When you register with WeCustomers.com, you create your own profile and privacy settings. Your profile information, as well as your first name, last initial and photo, are displayed to people in the WeCustomers.com community to enable you to connect with people on WeCustomers.com. We may occasionally use your name and email address to send you notifications regarding new services offered by WeCustomers.com that we think you may find valuable.

Profile information is used by WeCustomers.com primarily to be presented back to and edited by you when you access the service, and to be presented to others permitted by your privacy settings to view that information. In some cases, where your privacy settings permit it, other WeCustomers.com users may be able to supplement your profile.

WeCustomers.com reserves the right to send you notices about your account, even if you opt out of all voluntary email notifications.

WeCustomers.com may use information in your profile without identifying you as an individual to third parties. We may do this for purposes such as aggregating how many people in a particular network enjoy a band or product, and personalizing advertisements and promotions. We believe this benefits you
